<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Containers>
<Plugin>True</Plugin>
<PluginURL>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/desertwitch/NUT-unRAID/master/plugin/nut-dw.plg</PluginURL>
<PluginAuthor>desertwitch</PluginAuthor>
<Beta>False</Beta>
<Category>Tools:System Drivers:</Category>
<Name>Network UPS Tools (NUT) for UNRAID</Name>
<Description>
A refactored, modernized version of the original NUT plugin with a focus on frequent updates. This alternative version has improved usability through precise documentation, offering various NUT backends to choose from, and following the latest developments of the NUT master branch more closely. It strives to maximize both your UPS performance and compatibility, while also aiming to provide useful new features with the same amount of stability as in earlier versions.
</Description>
<Support>https://forums.unraid.net/topic/60217-plugin-nut-v2-network-ups-tools/</Support>
<Icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/desertwitch/NUT-unRAID/master/plugin/nut.png</Icon>
<Date>2023-09-04</Date>
<Changes>
###2023.09.02
- new: act on user configured notification triggers
- fix: improve logging for GUI actions
###2023.08.29
- new: user configuration now persists between reinstalls of the plugin
- new: added a button to GUI to reset all configuration files to their defaults
- new: defined safe zones for additional settings in the configuration files
- fix: clarified reload button in GUI some more for understanding what it does
- fix: minor changes in how copy operations of configuration files are handled
- fix: run UPS inverter poweroff also as root to avoid driver permission issues
- fix: nut scanner is now no longer breaking user configuration files
###2023.08.28
- new: refactored handling of permissions and wording of log messages
- new: refactored and decluttered installation, upgrading and removal processes
- new: improved upgrading process making sure all existing NUT services are stopped first
- new: compiled backend NUT package from current GitHub master branch (as of 26.08.2023)
- new: optimized backend NUT package to use folder structure of earlier releases
- new: added official Slackware Net-SNMP package with OpenSSL 3.1.2 for future UNRAID versions 6.13+
- new: added backend NUT package compiled with OpenSSL 3.1.2 for future UNRAID versions 6.13+
###2023.08.24
- new: compiled backend NUT package from current master branch (as of 24.08.2023)
</Changes>
</Containers>
